<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Carbot</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="gas_information_text">
        \n\n\n<b>Please note that these recommendations are general guidelines and actual heating savings may vary depending on individual circumstances.\n\n\n</b>

        \t\t\tYou can try the following methods to reduce the use of heating fuels:\n\n\n

- Lowering the temperature of your room by a few degrees can save energy.\n\n
- Utilize natural sunlight to naturally heat your rooms.\n\n
- Reduce energy losses by using windows and doors with improved insulation.\n\n
- Regular maintenance of your heating system can improve its efficiency.\n\n
- Consider alternative heating sources, such as solar energy or biomass.\n\n
- Save energy by turning off the heating system when rooms are not in use.\n\n
- Wearing insulated clothing can reduce the need for excessive heating.\n\n

\t\t\tBy implementing these simple steps, you can save energy and heat your space in a more environmentally friendly way. Remember, small changes can make a big difference.</string>

    <string name="water_information_text">
        \n\n\n<b>Please note that these recommendations are general guidelines and actual water savings may vary depending on individual circumstances.\n\n\n</b>

        \t\t\tYou can try the following methods to reduce water consumption:\n\n\n

- Fix any leaks in faucets, pipes, or toilets promptly.\n\n
- Install water-efficient fixtures and appliances, such as low-flow showerheads and dual-flush toilets.\n\n
- Take shorter showers and turn off the tap while brushing your teeth or washing dishes.\n\n
- Collect rainwater for watering plants and gardens.\n\n
- Use a broom instead of a hose to clean outdoor spaces like driveways and patios.\n\n
- Only run the dishwasher and washing machine with full loads.\n\n
- Consider installing a water-efficient irrigation system for your lawn.\n\n

\t\t\tBy adopting these practices, you can significantly reduce your water consumption and contribute to water conservation efforts. Remember, every drop counts!</string>

    <string name="electricity_information_text">
        \n\n\n<b>Please note that these recommendations are general guidelines and actual electricity savings may vary depending on individual circumstances.\n\n\n</b>

        \t\t\tYou can try the following methods to reduce electricity consumption:\n\n\n

- Turn off lights and appliances when not in use.\n\n
- Use energy-efficient light bulbs, such as LED or CFL bulbs.\n\n
- Unplug electronic devices and chargers when they are fully charged or not in use.\n\n
- Set your thermostat to an energy-saving temperature and use programmable thermostats.\n\n
- Use natural ventilation and ceiling fans instead of air conditioners whenever possible.\n\n
- Opt for energy-efficient appliances and electronics with high Energy Star ratings.\n\n
- Minimize the use of hot water by using cold water for laundry and shorter showers.\n\n

\t\t\tBy adopting these practices, you can significantly reduce your electricity consumption and contribute to energy conservation efforts. Remember, small changes in your habits can make a big difference!</string>


    <string name="sustainable_living_info">
<b>Principles of Sustainable Living and Its Importance:</b>\n\n\n

<b>1.</b> Sustainable Use of Resources:\n\n
- Acknowledge that natural resources are limited and future generations have the right to benefit from them.\n\n
- Utilize energy, water, forests, soil, and other resources efficiently and effectively.\n\n
- Reduce waste and consumption to ensure resources can sustain for a longer period.\n\n\n\n

<b>2.</b> Protecting the Environment and Supporting Natural Balance:\n\n
- Avoid activities that harm ecosystems and preserve natural habitats.\n\n
- Promote biodiversity and maintain natural balance by safeguarding species habitats.\n\n
- Embrace environmentally friendly practices to prevent water and air pollution.\n\n\n\n

<b>3.</b> Combating Climate Change:\n\n
- Reduce the use of fossil fuels to control greenhouse gas emissions.\n\n
- Transition to renewable energy sources and enhance energy efficiency.\n\n
- Opt for sustainable transportation options and minimize carbon footprint.\n\n\n\n

<b>4.</b> Supporting Social Justice and Community Well-being:\n\n
- Ensure everyone\'s basic needs are met and prioritize equality.\n\n
- Protect human rights and improve working conditions.\n\n
- Encourage community participation and ensure transparency in sustainability decision-making processes.\n\n\n\n

<b>5.</b> Long-Term Planning and Low-Carbon Economy:\n\n
- Embed sustainability principles at the core of economic activities.\n\n
- Develop sustainable development plans and manage resources in a balanced manner.\n\n
- Transition to a low-carbon economy and promote green job opportunities.\n\n\n\n

The principles of sustainable living are crucial for preserving nature, combating climate change, enhancing social welfare, and leaving a livable world for future generations. Implementing these principles enables us to take necessary steps towards a more sustainable future.

</string>

    <string name="others_information_text">
      \n\n\n  <b>Please note that these recommendations are general guidelines and actual waste reduction and recycling practices may vary depending on local regulations and facilities.</b>\n\n\n\n

        You can make a positive impact on the environment by following these methods to reduce waste and promote recycling:\n\n

        1. Reduce Consumption:\n\n
        - Purchase only what you need and avoid unnecessary packaging.\n\n
        - Choose durable and long-lasting products over disposable ones.\n\n
        - Say no to single-use items like plastic bags, straws, and utensils.\n\n
        - Bring your own reusable bags, water bottles, and coffee cups.\n\n\n\n

        2. Reuse and Repurpose:\n\n
        - Donate or sell items that are still in good condition but no longer needed.\n\n
        - Repair or refurbish broken or damaged items instead of throwing them away.\n\n
        - Get creative and find new uses for old items before discarding them.\n\n\n\n

        3. Recycle Properly:\n\n
        - Familiarize yourself with the recycling guidelines in your area.\n\n
        - Separate recyclable materials such as paper, plastic, glass, and metal.\n\n
        - Rinse out containers to remove any food residue before recycling.\n\n
        - Avoid contamination by not including non-recyclable items in your recycling bin.\n\n\n\n

        4. Compost Organic Waste:\n\n
        - Compost fruit and vegetable scraps, coffee grounds, and yard waste.\n\n
        - Use the resulting compost to enrich your soil and nourish your plants.\n\n\n\n

        5. Proper Disposal of Hazardous Materials:\n\n
        - Dispose of hazardous materials, such as batteries, electronic waste, and chemicals, at designated collection points or recycling facilities.\n\n
        - Follow local guidelines for the safe disposal of these items.\n\n

        By adopting these waste reduction and recycling practices, you can minimize your environmental impact, conserve resources, and contribute to a cleaner and healthier planet for future generations.
    </string>
</resources>